Guide to the David Sullivan U.S. Maoism Collection TAM 527
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VII: Organizational Printed Ephemera, 1938-2006
  - Students for a Democratic Society, 1964-1969 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Students for a Democratic Society: NY Regional Labor Committee, undated (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Sun Press, undated (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Support the Fired Nine (Babcock and Wilcox), undated (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Taxi Rank and File Coalition, undated (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Teamsters for a Democratic Union, undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Terrorist Information Project, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Theory and Practice, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Think Lincoln Committee (hospital workers), 1970 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Third World CUNY Coalition, undated (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Third World Student League, undated (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Third World Theory, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - TI Workers for a Union, undated (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Toufahn Organization, undated (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Trade Union Action and Democracy, 1971, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Trade Union/ Labor Work: Auto, undated (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Trade Union/ Labor Work: Electrical, undated (Box 16, Folder 60)
  - Trade Union/ Labor Work: Steel, undated (Box 16, Folder 61)
  - Trade Union/ Labor Work (unidentified union), undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Trade Union/ Labor Work (unidentified union): Fliers, undated (Box 16, Folder 62)
  - Tri-State Negro and Allied Trade Union Council, undated (Box 16, Folder 63)
  - Tudeh Party of Iran, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 64)
  - Tupelo Support Committee, undated (Box 16, Folder 65)
  - Tuscan Marxist-Leninist Collective, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 66)
  - Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee I, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee II, 1976-1977 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee, 1976-1978 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Union for Economic Justice, undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Union for Radical Political Economics (URPE), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Union Free Speech Defense Fund, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Union of Iranian Communists, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - United Committee of Unemployed People, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - United for Peace and Justice, undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - United Front Against Fascism (oral history transcript?), undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - United Front Against Imperialism, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - United Front for Attica, 1971, undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - United Front in Support of the Iranian People, undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - United Front: Jobs, undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - United Front Press, 1972-1974 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - United Graffiti Writers/ Artists, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - United League, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - United May Day Committee, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - United Mine Workers of America, circa 1974 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - United Rubber Workers, undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - United Workers Association, 1980-1981 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - United Workers Organization, undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - United Workers Organization: New York-New Jersey, 1976 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - US-China People's Friendship Association, 1974-1981 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - US Committee to Aid the National Liberation Front of South Vietnam, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - US Labor Party, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Venceremos, undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Vietnam, 1967-1970 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Vietnam, undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Vietnam Peace Parade Committee, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Vita Wa Watu (Boston busing), 1974 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Voice of the Health Worker, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - W.E.B. DuBois Clubs of America, 1965-1969 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - W.E.B. DuBois Clubs of America, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - W.E.B. DuBois Clubs of America: New York, undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Wei Min She: May Day, 1974 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - West Bronx Tenants Union/ Tenants, 1974, undated (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - "What is Class?", undated (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - White Blindspot Paper: Rebuttal, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - White Lightening (Bronx, NY), 1975 (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Women for Racial and Economic Equality (Chicago, IL), undated (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Women's Liberation and Marxism-Leninism, 1969-1970s (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Women's Union, undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - The Worker, 1960 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Workers' Books (Atlanta, GA), 1971-1972 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Workers Books (Philadelphia, PA), 1978 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Workers Committee for May Day, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Workers Committee to Smash the No-Strike Deal, undated (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Workers Congress (Marxist-Leninist), 1979 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Workers Defense Committee (San Francisco, CA), undated (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Workers Ex-Serviceman's League, undated (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Workers League, undated (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Workers Library Publishers (CPUSA Constitution), 1938 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Workers Organizing Committee at St. Luke's, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Workers Party of Japan, undated (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Workers Press (Taft-Hartley Slave Labor Law), undated (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Workers Viewpoint (New York, NY), 1974 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Workers World Army, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Working Women's Committee, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - World View Publishers (southern populism) (New York, NY), undated (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Wydell Trawick Justice Committee, undated (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Yenan Books, 1970s (Box 17, Folder 60)
  - Young Communist League, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Young Lord's Party, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - The Young Red, undated (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Young Socialist Alliance, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Young Workers Liberation League, 1971 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Youth in Action, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 66)
- Series VIII: Buttons, 1918-1984
  Series VIII contains hundreds of political buttons collected by David Sullivan. The buttons document campaigns by many of the organizations represented within Series I-VII and range in date from 1965-1984, though the majority are undated. There is a large selection of buttons with Chinese Communist Party symbols – red stars, hammers, and sickles, as well as pictures of Mao Tsetung. Buttons document congressional political campaigns in addition to events surrounding African Liberation Day, numerous boycotts, civil rights, gay rights, May Day, the Vietnam War, and the women's movement. A number of groups such as the Industrial Workers of the World, the Revolutionary Student Brigade, and the Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee have buttons in the collection. There are also buttons from unions and union elections. These come from the Communications Workers of America, the United Autoworkers, the United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers, and the United Steelworkers of America. Of note are three buttons, housed in a commemorative box, from the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (1918), a National Hunger March (1932), and the Steel Workers Organizing Committee (1937).
  - African Liberation Day (5 buttons), 1978, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Balanoff Campaigns (James - United Steelworkers of America) (Miriam - State Representative) (9 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Boycotts (Farah Pants, GE, Shell, United Farmworkers of America/lettuce, police brutality) (8 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Campaign Buttons (various unions - Frank McKee, Jack Parton) (8 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Civil Rights (Martin Luther King Jr., racism) (14 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Communications Workers of America (Final Warning, Local 1101) (6 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Communications Workers of America (Nationalize A.T.T.) (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Communist Party (Marxist-Leninist) (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Campaign (Harold Washington) (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Democratic Campaign (Bill Bork, Carol Mosley Braun, Katie Hall, McCarthy, McGovern, Mondale/Ferraro, Harold Washington) (17 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Democratic Party (7 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - District 65 (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Dobbs, Herbie (campaign for Griever - Division 1) (2 buttons), 1982 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - El Salvador (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Fateh (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Free Bobby Free Ericka All Power to the People (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Health Revolutionary Movement (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - I Wor Kuen (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Imperialism (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Industrial Workers of the World (4 buttons), 1984, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen and Helpers of America: Local 810 (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union: Cleveland (1 button), 1918 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Irish Political Prisoners (N.A.I.F) (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Local 65: Black Caucus (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Local 65: Black Caucus (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Mao Tsetung Images/ Chinese Communist Party Symbols (3 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Mao Tsetung Images/ Chinese Communist Party Symbols (21 buttons), 1979, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - March for Jobs (Washington DC) (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - March for Jobs Peace Freedom (Washington DC) (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - May Day (2 buttons), 1975-1979, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - May Day (19 buttons), 1975-1979, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Medical Committee for Human Rights (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous (9 buttons), 1965-1976, undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous (29 buttons), 1965-1976, undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous (8 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - National Coordinating Committee for Trade Union Action and Democracy (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - National Hunger March (1 button), 1932 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - National United Workers Organization (6 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Nixon, Richard (4 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Nuclear Power (4 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Palestine Solidarity (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Political Prisoners/ Police Oppression (John Artis and Rubin Carter, Starks and Pendleton, Tyrone Guyton, Bornson and Davis) (5 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Progressive Student Network (1 button), 1981 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Proud to be Union (4 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Puerto Rico (Young Lords Party) (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Reagan, Ronald (9 buttons), 1984, undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Reproductive Rights National Network (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Revolutionary Student Brigade/ Youth Protest Movements (6 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Solidarity Day (5 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Solidarity/ Solidarity Day (8 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - South African Liberation (5 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Steel Workers Organizing Committee C.I.O. Dues Paid for June (1 button), 1937 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Stop Fast Eddie (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Strike Fund (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Throw the Bum Out (Nixon) (7 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee (UWOC) (5 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - United Autoworkers (9 buttons), 1973, undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (3 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - United Mine Workers of America (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - United Steelworkers of America (8 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - United Steelworkers of America (8 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - United Workers' Association (3 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - United Workers' Association/ United Electrical (5 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - US-China Peoples Friendship Association (4 buttons), 1979, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - USSR out of Afghanistan (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Vietnam Veterans Against the War (5 buttons), 1967, undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Vietnam War (8 buttons), 1967, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - We've Carried the Rich for Two Hundred Years (7 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Women's Movement (4 buttons), 1970, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - The Worker (2 buttons), undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Workers' Throw the Bum Out! Committee (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Youth Against War and Fascism: Gay Caucus (1 button), undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Series IX: Posters, 1968-1990
  Series IX contains several hundred posters documenting the political events and organizations represented in Series I-VII. A portion of the posters were left folded and are in labeled folders, arranged by either organization or topic, while the rest were unrolled and are stored in flat files. The unrolled posters are currently in process and will be made available in 2012.
  - Sub-series A: Boxed
    - African Liberation Day Coalition, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Ashby Leach Defense Committee, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Attica Brigade, undated (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Black Liberation Month, 1981, undated (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Chicago May Day Coalition, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Cleveland Sign the Treaty Now Coalition, undated (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Coalition Against the Draft, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Committee in Solidarity with Southern Africa, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Committee to Support the Iranian People, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Communist Party (Marxist-Leninist): The Call/ El Clarin, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Frente del Pueblo, undated (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - International Women's Day, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - July 4th Coalition/ Rich Off Our Backs, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Mao Tsetung Memorial Committee, circa 1976 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - May 6th Coalition (nuclear power), undated (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Miners' Right to Strike Committee, 1977, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - National May Day Committee, 1980, undated (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - National United Workers Organization, undated (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - New Mobilization Against the Draft, undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Northeast Coalition for the Liberation of Southern Africa, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - People United to Fight Police Brutality, undated (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - People's Anti-War Mobilization, undated (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - People's Coalition for Peace and Justice (New York, NY), undated (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Poland, undated (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Prairie Fire, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Progressive Student Network, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Reagan, Ronald (anti-), undated (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Red Detachment of Women (ballet), undated (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Revolutionary Communist Party, 1979, undated (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Revolutionary Communist Party: Revolutionary Worker, undated (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Revolutionary Student Brigade, 1976, undated (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Revolutionary Union, undated (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Riverside Political Prisoners Defense Committee (Riverside, CA), undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Save County Hospital, undated (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Southern African Liberation Support Committee, undated (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Stop the Klan Defense Committee, undated (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Student Coalition to Stop the Selective Index, undated (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - Student Mobilization Committee to End the War in Vietnam, 1968 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - Tupelo Support Committee, undated (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Unemployed Workers Organizing Committee, 1976, undated (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - United May Day Committee, 1977, undated (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - US-China Peoples' Friendship Association of Chicago, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 41)
    - Vietnam Veterans Against the War, undated (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Sub-series B: Flat-Files (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13)
    - Anti-Bolshevik Advertising (Scot Tissue Towels), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder A-B)
    - Bohr, Niels (5 items, includes transparency) (signed by David Sullivan), 1987, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder A-B)
    - Brecht, Bertolt: "The Mother" (a play by the San Francisco Mime Troupe), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder A-B)
    - Buy War Bonds, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder A-B)
    - Chicago Women's Liberation Union (2 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder C)
    - Chile (3 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder C)
    - Chile Solidarity Committee (New York, NY), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder C)
    - China/ Chinese Communist Party, 1973-1975 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder C)
    - El Cine y la Guerra, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder C)
    - Cleveland Plain Dealer ("Newspaper Red Riot") (5 items, copies), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder C)
    - Cleveland Sign the Treaty Now Coalition (2 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder C)
    - Coalition to Stop Police Repression, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder C)
    - Committee for July 26 (Chicago, IL), 1974 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder C)
    - Countries Want Independence, Nations Want Liberation, People Want Revolution, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder C)
    - Engels, Friedrich (2 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder E-H)
    - Film Sovietico, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder E-H)
    - Guevara, Ernesto "Che" (Day of Heroic Guerilla), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder E-H)
    - Horn, Joshua Dr.: "Away with all pests...", undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder E-H)
    - Inauguracion de Cursos del Ano de 1979 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder I)
    - International Afrikan Women's Conference, 1974 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder I)
    - International Women's Day (3 items), 1981, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder I)
    - International Women's Day (October League) (3 copies), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder I)
    - International Women's Solidarity, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder I)
    - Ireland ("The Provisional Government of the Irish Republic to the People of Ireland...") (copy courtesy of the National Library), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder I)
    - Jackson, George (3 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder J-L)
    - Kampuchea (Concerts for the People of Kampuchea), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder J-L)
    - Kampuchea Support Committee (3 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder J-L)
    - Kampuchea Support (The Call) (2 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder J-L)
    - Kent State, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder J-L)
    - King, Martin Luther Jr., undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder J-L)
    - Lenin, V.I., undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder J-L)
    - Liberation Support Movement (Angola) (2 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder J-L)
    - Lozano, Rudy (memorial) (2 items), circa 1983 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder J-L)
    - Mao Tsetung (2 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 2, Folder M)
    - Marx, Karl (2 items), undated (Box XOS002, Folder M)
    - May Day Blast (2 items), 1990 (Box XOS002, Folder M)
    - May Day (Iranian Students Association in the U.S. (Houston, TX; Berkeley, CA), 1976 (Box XOS002, Folder M)
    - May Day (United May Day Committee) (3 items), undated (Box XOS002, Folder M)
    - Medical Aid for Indochina (Cambridge, MA), undated (Box XOS002, Folder M)
    - Midwest Coalition Against the Draft (Kent State 10th year anniversary) (Chicago, IL), 1980 (Box XOS002, Folder M)
    - National Liberation Front: Sisters in Solidarity, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder N-P)
    - New Communist Party, 1977 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder N-P)
    - Nicaragua, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder N-P)
    - October League (The Call), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder N-P)
    - October League (The Call/ El Clarin), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder N-P)
    - Palestine/ Vietnam One War One Victory (4 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder N-P)
    - Peace (United Artists), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder N-P)
    - People of the World Unite (2 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder N-P)
    - People's Movements around the World: International Teach-In (Chicago, IL), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder N-P)
    - Russia (in Russian) (29 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder R)
    - Sibeko, David Memorial, 1979 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder S-U)
    - Stalin, Joseph (2 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder S-U)
    - Stop the War Boston Common, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder S-U)
    - Tubman, Harriet Lives, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder S-U)
    - United Steelworkers of America (4 items), 1980, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder S-U (Oversize))
    - U.S.-China Peoples Friendship Association (New York, NY), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder S-U)
    - U.S. Committee of Women to Defend the Right to Live (solidarity with American women's liberation), circa 1970 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder S-U)
    - Vietnam (woman with gun), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder V-Y I)
    - Vietnam Veterans Against the War (20th Anniversary) (2 items), 1987 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder V-Y I)
    - Vietnam Veterans Against the War (Chicago, IL) (2 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder V-Y I)
    - Vietnam Veterans Against the War: Solidarity with Cambodian People (Chicago, IL), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder V-Y I)
    - Washington, Harold (election committees) (4 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder V-Y I)
    - Workers Solidarity Committee (2 items), undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder V-Y I)
    - World War II Anniversary (Slovak?), 1990 (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder V-Y I)
    - World War II (in German) (25 items), undated (Box XOS002, Folder V-Y II)
    - Young Patriots Organization, undated (Flat-file 6, Drawer 13, Folder V-Y I)
- Series X: Artifacts and Other Ephemera, 1965-1993
  Series X consists of the artifactual items found in the David Sullivan U.S. Maoism Collection. These are described at the folder, and at times, item level. Much of the material in this Series pertains to China and the Chinese Communist Party. There are several maps, sets of postcards, and travel guides pertaining to a presumed trip to China. There are also a number of visually striking scrolls, which depict scenes in China often involving communism and communist leaders.
  - Art Prints: China/ Chinese Communist Party, 1973-1976, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Art Prints: Rent Collection Courtyard: A Revolution in Sculpture, 1967 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Banners: Chinese Communism/ Mao Tsetung (3 items), undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Flag: China (1 item), undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Napoleon at Waterloo (game), 1979 (Box 19, Folder 44a)
  - Ornaments: Mao Tsetung and Zhou Enlai (2 items), undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Postcards: China (art), 1974 (Box 19, Folder 45)